ANDREY KHALETSKY

CONTACTS

Minsk city (ready for a relaunch)

+375(29)187-99-84

unking58@gmail.com

<u>linkedin.com/in/andrei-khaletski</u>

github.com/AndreiKhaletski

Junior Java Developer



EDUCATION

IT-Academy Educational Center for Programming and High Technologies:

Java Enterprise Development

01.2024 - 06.2024

Java Fundamentals

09.2023 - 12.2023

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics:

Artificial intelligence (Master's degree)

2021-2023

Information technology and management of technical systems

2016-2021

PROFILE

Graduated from the courses "Technologies for developing enterprise solutions in Java" and "Programming in Java"

At the university, he participated in the creation of an electronic educational resource for students. Studied applied computer science, intelligent systems, engineering and scientific computing systems (Matlab). At the university, participated in the creation of an electronic educational resource for students. Experience in assembling small mechatronic Festo systems with subsequent programming of controllers.

Good experience with Creo Parametric/GibbsCAM.

The level of English proficiency is Pre-intermediate.

Military status: reserve

SKILLS

- Java Core
- Spring
- SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL)
- JPA/Hibernate
- Maven, Gradle
- API (REST, Feign, Gateway, HTTP)
- Docker
- Postman
- Git

PROJECT

The project is a banking application that includes the ability to create an account for a user, add currency, create a user, view any information using pagination, register a user by sending a verification code to an email address, use a jwt token and delete an account or user. Also division into roles. Added auditing of some services. The project is assembled in Docker containers with a database, a proxy is used.

Project link:

https://github.com/AndreiKhaletski/ApplicationFinance.git

WORK EXPERIENCE

ADVIN Smart Factory Process Engineer

2023-present

LINEV GroupCNC adjuster

2019-2023